And Assalamu Alaikum, today is 28th August and
today we are going to talk about the quarterly results of ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company Limited.
Yes, the company has recently announced the total results of June
and in this video
we will know how the company has performed in its June quarter
results. So
before proceeding with the video, if
you have not yet subscribed to the channel, then
please subscribe to the channel and also
press the bell icon so that in future, if
I upload any video,
you get notifications. So
let's start the video
that ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company Limited is
sluggish. The company is doing straight. If you
look at the one-month graph, there is a
positive return of 3.89 percent, whereas if you look at the one-year graph, there is a positive return of
23.95 percent,
so it has given a decent return
compared to the period. So first of all, let's see what the company does,
as you understood from the name, it is
general insurance. ICICI
Lombard General Insurance is a
three-quarter company
and it belongs to the private sector.  If it is
non-life insurance,
then this is some such website
which comes under ICICI, this is it
and the
picture is some such that it
provides insurance like car insurance,
two wheeler insurance, travel insurance,
health insurance, cyber insurance, business insurance,
other and renewable, then
this is their website, so
if we talk about base, then the
price to earning ratio of tractor is 26.45, the
price to earning ratio of this company is
48.08, so the price of the sector
is already high from the point of view of the
company, in English, that is, according to the
validation, a
company will remain a bit expensive, if we talk about the profit statement of the sector, then it is
2.28, the
price to earning value of this company is
9.5, which is very high,
so let's take a look at their June
quarterly results, according to
screen mirror.in, if you go to the result of ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company Limited, then you can see that the profit of ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Limited
increased from Rs. 300 crore to Rs. 1000 crore in the June quarter.  The
operating
profit of these power companies has gone up, which was launched
in the March quarter and it got
converted into profit in the June quarter of Rs 192 crore.
If we talk about net profit, then
after taxation, they had a profit of Rs 3.6 crore
in the March quarter, that
net profit has almost halved to Rs 152 crore in the June quarter. The
reason for this is that their
expenses have been increased on the next phase and at the same time, they have
imposed a lot of tax on their individuals.
You can see in the last market quarter that their base was quite
good. Even though there was a decrease in revenue in their core business,
but in their
source of respect income, Dadar, they
showed a good pocket of Rs 466 crore, so
due to this the result is good. The result of Night Politics was
of crore rupees, well the
profit net profit fell and this time only Rs
10 crore and respect income, so the result is Rs
150 crore and two crore rupees net profit, so
you can say that  Ravindra Chhabra said that the
net profit between Aishwarya and operating
profit was also good, which means that
their business is growing, only other income has
reduced a little, or even a lot, due to which
their
Jio net profit is less than the previous quarter, so the
result is neither good nor bad,
whereas if we talk about pros and cons,
then the positive point is that this company is almost
free, and the profit
growth rate of the company is quite good, at a
rate of 23 percent in the last five years, the
company has given out a profit of
17.2%, great, from
a minute point, if we talk about the
shareholding pattern of the company, the promoter has
reduced his holding of 4%,
in the last two-three years it is
not considered good because the
promoters are internal to the
company and if the promoters of the company are
reducing their stake
in the company, it means that they are
seeing some shortcomings in the company, some
irregularities,
due to which  If you are reducing your stake and
want to exit by selling it, then there is a negative point. At the same time,
if we talk about the intrinsic value of this company,
then according to a tip, the
entry value of Lambert Lombard General Insurance Company Limited from ICI is
also expensive. If this company falls a little down, then
you can purchase it,
but right now it is expensive.
Talking about the liquidity issue, FD has given good returns.
Talking about
dividend, this company has given different returns but has
not given that good dividend. There are no
side effects from the entry point.
According to the tips,
if we talk about the shareholding pattern, then the company has 0.91 percent
shareholding. The mutual
fund has a holding of 986 percent, which is a
good holding, but you will notice one thing that
in the last several quarters, the jewellery has
continuously reduced its holding, so this can be
called a negative point of it. But
still, the building of the mutual fund is quite good, it is
fine. The two-match series
station has a holding of 0.90%,
whereas the foreign station  It is a
29.75 percent building and retail has a
holding of 724 percent.
So this was my video on the June quarter results of ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company Limited.
How did you like the video? If you found it a little informative, then
please like the video
or if you have not yet subscribed to the channel, then
please subscribe to the channel
so that
when I upload such regular videos, you
get a notification and do
tell me in the comment section at which
stage of these features you want the video
and then we will meet with the next video and of these on